It's been a while.
久しぶりです
久 し ぶりです
Eh, are you okay?
え、大丈夫?
I couldn't make a sound right now.
今声が出てなかったです
Oh, are you nervous?
あ、緊張してますか?
I'm nervous.
緊張してます
I think I did it last time, but I was still a little nervous.
やっぱり前回やったと思うけど、 それはまだちょっと緊張して
Ru?
る?
It makes me nervous.
緊 張しますね
One by one they started to look alike.
1つずつ似てまいったもんね
pretty.
かなり
It's good to say it like this.
こうやっていうのがいいね
I'm wearing something really sexy today
今日はなんかめっちゃセクシーな服で
You can see it, right?
見 えてるんじゃないですか?
I could see it.
見えちゃいましたね
I'm sorry, but
せっかくなんですけど、
I contacted you again and asked you to come.
もう 一回連絡させてもらって、 来てもらったんですけど、
I'm not feeling like myself today.
今日はちょっと僕じゃないんですよ、
actually.
実は
I called an acquaintance over, hey.
知り合い呼んだんですよ、ちょっと
I called someone I knew, and I met that person.
知り合い呼んだんで、 その人と
I want you to do it.
して ほしいなって
It's like, I want to see you doing something.
ちょっとしてるとこ見たいな、みたいな
I don't think you can see it because it's a little hidden behind me.
ちょっと俺の後ろに隠れてるから 見えないと思うけど、
Would you like me to stand next to you for a moment?
一瞬横についてもらう?
Sideways for a moment.
一瞬横に
See, you were there, right?
ほら、いたでしょ?
I didn't understand.
分かんなかった
I had a double.
分身したんだけど
I want you to do something with this person today.
この人と一緒なことを 今日はしてほしいなって
Does it look okay?
大丈夫そうかな?
I don't think you can talk to me.
僕と喋ってもらえないと思うので
nice to meet you.
初めまして
But that's it.
でもあれですね
That's not true.
違いますね
It's even cuter.
より可愛いですね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Do you even think of yourself as cute?
自分でも思いますか、自分のこと可愛い?
a little bit.
ちょっと
It's good to be honest.
素直でいいですね
Her eyes are cute.
目元が可愛いですね
I arrived 5 minutes ago.
5分前に来てしまったんですが、
Because there is space.
ス ペースがあるので
yes.
はい
Suddenly on the head.
いきなりヘッドに
Oh, that?
あ、あれ?
It's piling up.
溜まってますね
How about it again?
改めてどうですか?
It's cute, isn't it?
可愛いですよね
I think it's really cute when you look at this dimensional threat.
やっぱりこの次元脅威で見ると すごい可愛いなと思います
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Well, I'm suddenly inviting you to bed, so that's what happened.
もうね、いきなりベッドに誘っているので あれなんですけど、
You don't have to worry about me.
僕のことは気にしないでいいんで
Don't you want to make a mess of it?
めちゃめちゃ歯立てしろくないですか?
Is it true?
本当ですか?
It's a mess.
めちゃめちゃね
picture?
え?
It was the head.
頭でした
Is it wine red?
ワインレッドですか?
It's wine red.
ワインレッドです
I just finished confirming that I can wear underwear.
下着履けるという確認も終わったところで
It feels good.
いい感触です
These are my favorite lips.
好きな唇です
It's C.
Cです
That's nice.
いいですね
It's a modern trend.
現代の流行りですね
It's not bad.
やばくないですね
It would be nice if the answer was straightforward.
返答がストレートでいいですね
Where do you feel it?
どこら辺が感じますか?
It's nearby.
近くです
feeling
感じ
Will you?
ます か?
I feel it.
感じます
What's below?
下は?
It's a repeat.
繰りとりです
thank you.
ありがとうございます
This way.
こっち
I see.
なるほど
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいですね
It's okay to be beautiful.
綺麗なんて大丈夫ですよ
Is it that embarrassing?
そんなに恥ずかしい?
Butt muscles.
尻筋が
I have a big waist.
腰が大きい
One step away.
一歩すぐ
Is it underwear?
下着ですか?
Do you like your favorite underwear?
好きな下着は好きですか?
I like it.
好きです
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
This is dangerous, isn't it?
これやばいでしょ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Do you have weak armpits?
脇弱いですか?
Armpits are weak.
脇弱い
Do you like armpits?
脇好きなんですか?
He's really good at table tennis though.
卓球にめちゃくちゃ力強いんだけど
Is it on your side?
脇ですか?
yes.
はい
like.
好き
Do cute girls like armpits too?
かわいい女の子も脇が好きなんですか?
A chewy scent.
かむきつけの香り
Can't you feel your armpits?
脇は感じないですか?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
The armpits and legs are sexy.
脇は足元がセクシーです
difficult.
難しい
Ah, here.
あ、ここ
It's here.
ここなんだ
It would be nice if you could write it straight.
ストレートの書いておくと嬉しいです
Even in my underwear.
下着の中も
shame
恥
Zuka
ず か
Yes.
しい
It's embarrassing.
恥 ずかしい
恥 ず か しい
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Her nipples are played with and licked.
乳首はいじられるのと舐めるの
Lick it.
舐めるのです
I get licked.
舐められるの
I prefer being licked.
舐められたほうが好き
That's right.
そうなんだ
It's not in there at all.
そこ全然入ってないです
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
I want to check it out.
チェックしたいな
What are you checking?
何のチェックですか?
Check the lining.
裏地チェック
amazing.
すごい
A fragrant smell.
香ばしい匂い
I can't see it.
見えない
You might not be able to see it because it's dark.
暗いから見えないかもしれないけど
It's a little damp.
若干湿ってますね
But it's dark.
暗いからだけど
Spread your legs.
足広げて
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
It's so beautiful.
めちゃくちゃ綺麗ですよ
amazing.
すごい
It looks great on camera.
カメラにすごい映ってる
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいです
It's small.
ちっちゃいね
Haven't you seen it yourself?
自分で見たことない?
No.
ないです
I've never seen it before.
見たことないんだ
It's so tiny.
すごいちっちゃい
Where to put the chin chin.
チンチン入れるところ
What do you put the chin chin in?
チンチン入れるのは何ですか?
This is the hole where you insert your pussy.
マンコマをチンチン入れる穴です
I received it.
いただきました
lick
舐
I met you.
め たね
I licked it.
舐めた
terrible.
やばい
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
It might be dangerous.
やばいかもしれない
I might go.
行っちゃうかもしれない
I might go somewhere.
どっか行っちゃうかもしれない
I might go.
行っちゃうかもしれない
hang on.
待って
Really.
本当に
Can you see where my finger is?
指が入ってるところ見える?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Shall we go?
行ってみようか
Chinchin, I'm so happy.
チンチン、嬉しいですって
what?
何ですか?
Why?
何で?
Why did you do it?
何でやったんでしょう?
Last time, it just flowed a bit and it turned out that way.
前はちょっと流れてそうなっちゃったっていう
Flowing?
流れて?
Did it flow like that?
流れてそうなっちゃった?
It feels good, right?
気持ちいいでしょ?
That's what I'm saying.
言ってるじゃん
Just a little bit.
ちょっとだけ
Yeah.
うん
terrible.
やばい
Looks like it's about time to go.
そろそろ行きそうだ
Are you about to come out?
出ちゃいそうなんですか?
Looks like it's about to come out.
出ちゃいそう
Come to life.
生え出して
Is it okay?
いいの?
Please release a lot of sperm.
いっぱい精子出してください
Did you suddenly move on?
急に先ばたったの?
In this.
この中に
Please release a lot of sperm.
いっぱい精子出してください
Then I'll give you a lot.
じゃあいっぱい出すよ
I'll go.
行くよ
The first thing I said was, ``What's wrong?'' I want to take it out.
なんか最初の 何はダメとか 外に出してみたいな 言ってな
Was it?
かった っけ?
Huh?
あれ?
Before the last sperm comes out
なんか 最後に精子出る前
Did you say that?
言 ってたの?
Please release as much sperm as possible into my thoughts.
私の 思うことの中に 精子 いっぱい出してください
why?
なんで?
Take it out
出して
please.
ください
That's right.
そうだ よね
that's why
だから
What was it like when the sperm came out?
さ 精子さ 出たときさ どんな感じだった?
It felt good.
気持ちよかった
Did it feel good?
気持ちよかった?
It felt good. That's right. It feels good.
気持ちよかったって それさ 気持ちいいとか当たってるって 子
Miya: I think it's a hit.
宮 とかに当たってるとかじゃん
The sperm hit the uterus.
精子に子宮に当たってんじゃん
That's probably dangerous.
危ないよそれ多分
It's dangerous.
危 ないよ
Didn't you knock?
ノックしたんじゃない?
It might not work.
ダメかも
ダメかもね
I had a lot of sperm poured into my pussy.
マンコの中に いっぱい精子注いで もらいました
ERROR
この中に いっぱい精子注いで もらいました
The creampie edge felt good.
中出しエッジ気持ちよかったです